/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8300c817f0398f9d3d6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "I think these technical definitions of IT can’t seem to break away from the modern concepts of technology. We did not start with computers. When we define IT we must consider just what is it that we are doing: our major goal is the sharing of information. Certainly the creation of language improved our ability to do just that. There are other considerations, the definitions given mention software. Well what else is language but software? The next question is: Is it technology? The first two definitions of technology given by Merriam-Webster’s online dictionary are a :  the practical application of knowledge especially in a particular area b :  a capability given by the practical application of knowledge. Clearly pre-linguistic man made a practical application of his knowledge to create lan Continue Reading I think these technical definitions of IT can’t seem to break away from the modern concepts of technology. We did not start with computers. When we define IT we must consider just what is it that we are doing: our major goal is the sharing of information. Certainly the creation of language improved our ability to do just that. There are other considerations, the definitions given mention software. Well what else is language but software? The next question is: Is it technology? The first two definitions of technology given by Merriam-Webster’s online dictionary are a :  the practical application of knowledge especially in a particular area b :  a capability given by the practical application of knowledge. Clearly pre-linguistic man made a practical application of his knowledge to create lan Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:34:08.437Z"),
    "question" : "What is information technology and why is it called that? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8560c817f0398f9d3ee"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-information-technology-and-why-is-it-called-that?-",
    "answer" : "I think these technical definitions of IT can’t seem to break away from the modern concepts of technology. We did not start with computers. When we define IT we must consider just what is it that we are doing: our major goal is the sharing of information. Certainly the creation of language improved our ability to do just that. There are other considerations, the definitions given mention software. Well what else is language but software? The next question is: Is it technology? The first two definitions of technology given by Merriam-Webster’s online dictionary are a :  the practical application of knowledge especially in a particular area b :  a capability given by the practical application of knowledge. Clearly pre-linguistic man made a practical application of his knowledge to create lan Continue Reading I think these technical definitions of IT can’t seem to break away from the modern concepts of technology. We did not start with computers. When we define IT we must consider just what is it that we are doing: our major goal is the sharing of information. Certainly the creation of language improved our ability to do just that. There are other considerations, the definitions given mention software. Well what else is language but software? The next question is: Is it technology? The first two definitions of technology given by Merriam-Webster’s online dictionary are a :  the practical application of knowledge especially in a particular area b :  a capability given by the practical application of knowledge. Clearly pre-linguistic man made a practical application of his knowledge to create lan Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:34:46.119Z"),
    "question" : "What is information technology and why is it called that? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8690c817f0398f9d3f8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-information-systems-and-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Both information systems (IS) and information technology (IT) are burgeoning industries that offer job opportunities that have long-term professional growth potential. The fields are related in more ways than that, however. In fact, the terms information technology and information systems are sometimes used interchangeably, but that is a misnomer. There are similarities and differences in the two fields. Information Technology IT is a wide-ranging term that describes the technological transfer, storage and accessibility of information. Thus, IT falls under the IS umbrella — it deals with the technological components that are used in the information systems themselves. By definition, IT is the study, design, implementation, support or management of computer-based information systems. Speaking  Continue Reading Both information systems (IS) and information technology (IT) are burgeoning industries that offer job opportunities that have long-term professional growth potential. The fields are related in more ways than that, however. In fact, the terms information technology and information systems are sometimes used interchangeably, but that is a misnomer. There are similarities and differences in the two fields. Information Technology IT is a wide-ranging term that describes the technological transfer, storage and accessibility of information. Thus, IT falls under the IS umbrella — it deals with the technological components that are used in the information systems themselves. By definition, IT is the study, design, implementation, support or management of computer-based information systems. Speaking  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:35:05.529Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between information systems and information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8820c817f0398f9d404"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-my-career-options-after-taking-information-technology-degree?-",
    "answer" : "Well, you are asking a question which can be answered in several ways. you have to be specific about what you have, what you want and what you need in IT. I am assuming jobs in IT. Let me give you a basic - very high level example. IT - > 1. Hardware (HW) 2. Software (SW) Under 1. HW (a big ocean) a. Intel platform (Desktops/laptops/Servers etc) - these are CISC (Complex Instruction Set Computing) based computing b. Others - Apple Mac, IBM mainframe (Apple Desktops / servers/ IBM Servers) etc - These are RISC (Reduced Instruction Set Computing) based computing & c. there is the other which is called Non-Stop Servers which are in between these two computing (RISC & CISC) for high availability. these are used in Banks / ATM’s etc. Then comes Storage/Datacenter/Networking and the list goes on… you hav Continue Reading Well, you are asking a question which can be answered in several ways. you have to be specific about what you have, what you want and what you need in IT. I am assuming jobs in IT. Let me give you a basic - very high level example. IT - > 1. Hardware (HW) 2. Software (SW) Under 1. HW (a big ocean) a. Intel platform (Desktops/laptops/Servers etc) - these are CISC (Complex Instruction Set Computing) based computing b. Others - Apple Mac, IBM mainframe (Apple Desktops / servers/ IBM Servers) etc - These are RISC (Reduced Instruction Set Computing) based computing & c. there is the other which is called Non-Stop Servers which are in between these two computing (RISC & CISC) for high availability. these are used in Banks / ATM’s etc. Then comes Storage/Datacenter/Networking and the list goes on… you hav Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:35:30.961Z"),
    "question" : "What are my career options after taking information technology degree? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8950c817f0398f9d40d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-subjects-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "There you go!  Data StructuresDiscrete Structures and Graph TheoryComputer Based Numerical and Statistical TechniquesDigital Logic and DesignSoft ComputingMultimedia and AnimationOperating SystemsTheory of Automaton and Formal LanguagesInformation Theory and CodingCyber SecurityWeb techDesign and Analysis of AlgorithmsDatabase Management SystemsPrinciples of Programming LanguagesManagement of Information SystemsComputer NetworksSoftware EngineeringCompiler DesignArtificial IntelligenceDistributed SystemsCryptography and Network SecurityThe above are all the mandatory subjects. Apart from these, there will be open electives for you in the 6th, 7th and the 8th semester. These are as follows:- Elective 1- Software Quality EngineeringSoftware TestingSoftware Reliability Elective 2- Parallel AlgoriContinue Reading There you go!  Data StructuresDiscrete Structures and Graph TheoryComputer Based Numerical and Statistical TechniquesDigital Logic and DesignSoft ComputingMultimedia and AnimationOperating SystemsTheory of Automaton and Formal LanguagesInformation Theory and CodingCyber SecurityWeb techDesign and Analysis of AlgorithmsDatabase Management SystemsPrinciples of Programming LanguagesManagement of Information SystemsComputer NetworksSoftware EngineeringCompiler DesignArtificial IntelligenceDistributed SystemsCryptography and Network SecurityThe above are all the mandatory subjects. Apart from these, there will be open electives for you in the 6th, 7th and the 8th semester. These are as follows:- Elective 1- Software Quality EngineeringSoftware TestingSoftware Reliability Elective 2- Parallel AlgoriContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:35:49.332Z"),
    "question" : "What are subjects in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8a90c817f0398f9d417"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-future-of-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Advancements in the Information Technology Field: The taking care of, control and the officials of data using PC can in like manner be described as an Information Technology. As a name of a professional education program, it implies the arranging of possibility to meet the PC innovation necessities of the business, social protection, government, establishments, and various sorts of affiliations. The opening in IT fields is furthermore growing a direct result of the variety of execution of IT specialists in each field. The recently referenced explanation moreover urge IT undertakings to give occupations upon an extensive scale. IT division can be said as a pot of chances that allow one to accomplish top in an understudy's life. A calling in IT is seen as a champion among the most rewarding o Continue Reading Advancements in the Information Technology Field: The taking care of, control and the officials of data using PC can in like manner be described as an Information Technology. As a name of a professional education program, it implies the arranging of possibility to meet the PC innovation necessities of the business, social protection, government, establishments, and various sorts of affiliations. The opening in IT fields is furthermore growing a direct result of the variety of execution of IT specialists in each field. The recently referenced explanation moreover urge IT undertakings to give occupations upon an extensive scale. IT division can be said as a pot of chances that allow one to accomplish top in an understudy's life. A calling in IT is seen as a champion among the most rewarding o Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:36:09.318Z"),
    "question" : "What is the future of Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8cf0c817f0398f9d428"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-latest-technology-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Here I gave some predictions for latest information technologies and to know more about this visit this article. Technology predictions for 2018 The most important 2017 was a dark year for the technology industry, dotted with cool new gadgets, predictable breakthroughs and spectacular failures What will 2018 bring? Here are some of our predictions Wait for new advances in virtual reality that you can access from your phone (CNN Money) - 2017 was a dark year for the technology industry, dotted with cool new gadgets, predictable breakthroughs and spectacular failures. What will 2018 bring? Here are some of our predictions. 1. Virtual reality  It was assumed that virtual reality was going to take over the world. But tie a pair of glasses to the head and watch video games or 360 videos is not what many exp Continue Reading Here I gave some predictions for latest information technologies and to know more about this visit this article. Technology predictions for 2018 The most important 2017 was a dark year for the technology industry, dotted with cool new gadgets, predictable breakthroughs and spectacular failures What will 2018 bring? Here are some of our predictions Wait for new advances in virtual reality that you can access from your phone (CNN Money) - 2017 was a dark year for the technology industry, dotted with cool new gadgets, predictable breakthroughs and spectacular failures. What will 2018 bring? Here are some of our predictions. 1. Virtual reality  It was assumed that virtual reality was going to take over the world. But tie a pair of glasses to the head and watch video games or 360 videos is not what many exp Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:36:47.938Z"),
    "question" : "What is the latest technology in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8e40c817f0398f9d433"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-best-branch-in-information-technology-field?-",
    "answer" : "Parath Sharma While IT and CS degrees can lead to similar jobs, the differences between the two are quite pronounced. IT professionals should enjoy installing computer systems, using software and maintaining networks and databases, while computer scientists should enjoy mathematics and software design.  But most of job whether it consists of installation of computer system, using software and maintaining networks or enjoyment in mathematics and software design, both needs a great deal of coding. Talking abut the software development industry, it’s one of the most welcoming industry with wide sectors of choices. Whether its Web Development, Mobile Development or Data Sciences, IT professionals are everywhere. Talking about the software development industry, generally there are top 3 fields in it, Web DevelopContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:37:08.501Z"),
    "question" : "What is the best branch in information technology field? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e8f80c817f0398f9d440"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-impact-of-information-technology-on-society?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the impact of information technology on society?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:37:28.177Z"),
    "question" : "What is the impact of information technology on society? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e90c0c817f0398f9d44a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-scope-of-IT?-",
    "answer" : "Manohar Tm Are you looking for the Scope in Information Technology in India? Do you know how much does a single IT Professional earns per month? How is the job opportunities available for IT candidates in India? For all such information, do check this content on “Scope and Salary of IT (information technology) in India”. Computer Science Engineering and Information Technology leads the world to different dimensions. Without using these technologies and innovations, there won’t be any development in the computer world. Information Technology got many branches. The basic cluster will be Software and Hardware course. For the certificate course, you can go with Diploma, Post Graduation Diploma, Bachelor Degree, Post Graduation and Ph.D. In India, many UGC affiliated colleges are offering these UG and PG co Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:37:48.041Z"),
    "question" : "What are the scope of IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e91f0c817f0398f9d454"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-exact-difference-between-Information-technology-and-computer-science?-",
    "answer" : "Ioannis Kourouklides Several people gave their perspective. I still believe that the answer was not clearly or fully answered, so I will try to give my perspective. The definition I will use for Computer Science (CS) will be the one used by most of the Top 100 universities in the world rankings. Many other universities will follow it too. Computer Science To begin with, CS is an academic discipline. It very rare that you will find companies asking to recruit for ‘Computer Scientist’ jobs. Many times companies will require such a degree or a relevant one, but the job title will be different. At the link below you can find an excellent presentation with 10 myths busted:10 Myths for Computer Science Despite its name, a significant amount of CS does not involve the study of computers themselves. A famous quotation sta Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:38:07.236Z"),
    "question" : "What is the exact difference between Information technology and computer science? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e9320c817f0398f9d45e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-hard-to-study-IT?-",
    "answer" : "In 20 years of my IT career, I worked on ERP, ETL, BI and Big Data technologies .I did not work on any technology for more than a year. In ERP, I worked on Baan for a year and then MFG-Pro for almost another year. Knowing the business functionality, it was not difficult for me to pick up a tool but every time you need to start from scratch as the feature of every tool is different though functionality is same. When we were at customer site, then we did not have time to do research on the tool and immediately we have to fix the bugs. If you work on one tool for more than years then you become expert and proficient. In ETL there are many tools like Informatica, Data stage, AB Initio and SSIS. I had worked on almost every tool for smaller period as per company needs but did not get a chance to Continue Reading In 20 years of my IT career, I worked on ERP, ETL, BI and Big Data technologies .I did not work on any technology for more than a year. In ERP, I worked on Baan for a year and then MFG-Pro for almost another year. Knowing the business functionality, it was not difficult for me to pick up a tool but every time you need to start from scratch as the feature of every tool is different though functionality is same. When we were at customer site, then we did not have time to do research on the tool and immediately we have to fix the bugs. If you work on one tool for more than years then you become expert and proficient. In ETL there are many tools like Informatica, Data stage, AB Initio and SSIS. I had worked on almost every tool for smaller period as per company needs but did not get a chance to Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:38:26.340Z"),
    "question" : "Is it hard to study IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e9440c817f0398f9d468"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-Computer-Engineering-and-Information-Technology-and-if-there-is-any-then-why-both-have-same-syllabus-in-india?-",
    "answer" : "CSE(Computer Science & Engineering) and IT (Information technology) both are quite similar in some or the other manner. I always have come across students who are confused between these two fields because of the lack of the understanding of the minute differences and similarities between the two engineering streams. Main Difference : CSE: Computer science engineers are involved in many aspects of computing, from the design of individual microprocessors, personal computers and supercomputers to circuit designing and writing software that powers them. IT: Information Technology deals with the use of electronic computers and computer software to store, protect process, transmit and securely retrieve data. IT professionals perform a variety of tasks that range from installing applications to desi Continue Reading CSE(Computer Science & Engineering) and IT (Information technology) both are quite similar in some or the other manner. I always have come across students who are confused between these two fields because of the lack of the understanding of the minute differences and similarities between the two engineering streams. Main Difference : CSE: Computer science engineers are involved in many aspects of computing, from the design of individual microprocessors, personal computers and supercomputers to circuit designing and writing software that powers them. IT: Information Technology deals with the use of electronic computers and computer software to store, protect process, transmit and securely retrieve data. IT professionals perform a variety of tasks that range from installing applications to desi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:38:44.879Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between Computer Engineering and Information Technology and if there is any then why both have same syllabus in india? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e96b0c817f0398f9d483"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Discuss-the-major-role-of-mathematics-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Scott Ketter, B.S. Information Technology, Capella University (2018)Answered 1 year agoDiscuss the major role of mathematics in information technology? Scott Ketter Some areas of information technology have significantly more math involved than others. For example, video game development with it’s various physics simulations and intense graphics. Software development in general uses a fair amount of math. Network and systems administration use math for calculating IP addresses available in a given network, etc.. Since the fundamentals of information technology operate on logical systems where math is intrinsic to their operations, it may be difficult to find a single area of information technology that does not use math. Before we had digital computers, math mathematicians were kind of like software developers. They could develop a series of formulas and equations that took numbers as the input and delivered numbers as an output to represent some sort  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:39:23.571Z"),
    "question" : "Discuss the major role of mathematics in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e9910c817f0398f9d490"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-information-technology-same-as-information-science?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is information technology same as information science?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:40:01.786Z"),
    "question" : "Is information technology same as information science? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e9b60c817f0398f9d4a6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-an-MBA-in-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Santosh Nadagouda, studied Information TechnologyAnswered 4 years ago · Author has 99 answers and 257.1K answer viewsWhat is an MBA in Information Technology? Santosh Nadagouda I will say MBA in Information technology is of equal importance to BE in Information technology. MBA IT is about Business processes with information technology. Its about automating Business Processes like MarketingFinanceHRProductionOperationMarket Research etcIts about creating systems aiming less manual work and all that user has to do - is to provide inputs and system takes it from there as simple as that. MBA Information technology has all JOB ORIENTED Subjects. E-COMMERCEProject ManagementData WarehousingERP(SAP if lucky)Software Engineering ManagementNetworkingBusiness Intelligence etcPick any of these and you shall have good career prospects. MBA IT grads usually get Business Analyst, Functional Consultant, Technical Support Specialist. There is lot more Job satisfaction. If you know pr Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:40:38.897Z"),
    "question" : "What is an MBA in Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e9c80c817f0398f9d4ad"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-does-information-technology-improve-business?-",
    "answer" : "There are three ways that information technology improves business.The first is the support of the primary business process, the chain of activities that creates value.I did stock administration with pen and paper and using a computer for that task removed a lot of errors in the process. I’ve also worked in bookkeeping and doing it by hand is annoying. I’ve moved manual order confirmation in a trading process to a systems based order confirmation. Here we find direct benefits of putting tasks in a system. The second improvement is by generating data on the primary process.Once you have the data in a system, you can run an analysis over the data. You might find trends that you could not reveal.For example, withing the order confirmation process we could see how many orders were processed Continue Reading There are three ways that information technology improves business.The first is the support of the primary business process, the chain of activities that creates value.I did stock administration with pen and paper and using a computer for that task removed a lot of errors in the process. I’ve also worked in bookkeeping and doing it by hand is annoying. I’ve moved manual order confirmation in a trading process to a systems based order confirmation. Here we find direct benefits of putting tasks in a system. The second improvement is by generating data on the primary process.Once you have the data in a system, you can run an analysis over the data. You might find trends that you could not reveal.For example, withing the order confirmation process we could see how many orders were processed Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:40:56.939Z"),
    "question" : "How does information technology improve business? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034e9fd0c817f0398f9d4d1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-computer-science-engineering-and-information-technology-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between information technology and computer science & engineering?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:41:49.393Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between information technology and computer science & engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ea0f0c817f0398f9d4dc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-business-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is business information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:42:07.743Z"),
    "question" : "What is business information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ea430c817f0398f9d4f7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-information-system-and-information-technology-the-same-things?-",
    "answer" : "Khushi GautamAnswered 7 months ago · Author has 195 answers and 51K answer viewsAre information system and information technology the same things? Khushi Gautam Information technology is considered the study, design, implementation, support, and management of computer-based information systems. Its primary focus was on maintaining the system's hardware, software, databases, and networks, with the final goal of delivering to users, how to best utilize its functionality. An online IT degree encourages students to think critically and innovatively solve business problems through technology. It includes a breadth of disciplines, including computer software, cyber and data security, and project management. Information systems refer to the management of an entire set of information, including the technical elements involved with people and processes. Information degree systems coursework ranges from programming to communications, to help students learn b Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:42:59.261Z"),
    "question" : "Are information system and information technology the same things? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ea550c817f0398f9d50e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-did-Rahul-Gulati-from-Jaypee-Institute-of-Information-Technology-get-hired-by-Facebook-and-then-by-Google?-",
    "answer" : "Prakhar Mittal I was reached out by Google, Facebook, and a few more companies, mainly because of my achievements in programming competitions. I was among the top 500 in each of Google CodeJam (Round II), TopCoder Open (Round II), and Facebook HackerCup (Round III) in the year when these companies reached me out. These companies do reach out to potential candidates for job opportunities if they do well in the programming competitions organized by them. I did prepare a lot for these interviews and I will give you my advice on how you could go about doing the same. Programming Literature You would need to develop a good amount of expertise in a programming language of your choice. The most commonly used languages are C/C++ and Java, so I'll be recommending literature only for these. For C/C++, I'd recommend C Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:43:17.431Z"),
    "question" : "How did Rahul Gulati from Jaypee Institute of Information Technology get hired by Facebook and then by Google? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ea6a0c817f0398f9d519"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-Information-technology-and-software-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between Information technology and software engineering?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:43:38.446Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between Information technology and software engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ea8f0c817f0398f9d530"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-a-career-in-information-technology-worth-it?-",
    "answer" : "Questions Mahesh Shrestha",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:44:14.999Z"),
    "question" : "Is a career in information technology worth it? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eaa20c817f0398f9d538"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-next-big-thing-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Rahul Khachane, Assistant Professor  (2018-present)Answered 3 years ago · Author has 293 answers and 595.3K answer viewsWhat is the next big thing in information technology? Rahul Khachane The next big leap in information technology is already underway. It is blockchain technology. There was always a concern in human history that how one could verify the originality of information or anything. Information Technology is vulnerable to manipulation and modifications. This in itself creates a unique problem in using information technology and computers. Blockchain technology beautifully developed a complex algorithm which is open source. It creates blocks using host of events happening in digital world. Each block is unique in the world and can be identified without any efforts. By using this technology every bit of information can be identified and verified. It is a revolution as big as internet itself. Sooner it will change the way information is transmitted and handled. While this  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:44:34.226Z"),
    "question" : "What is the next big thing in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eab30c817f0398f9d542"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-current-status-of-Information-Technology-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "IndiaNetzone gives idea about I T in INdia: BUT— Information Technology in India, Communication in India Information Technology in India is a key driver of the economic growth in the nation. BUT_ ALL IS NOT WELL,,,It appears to be bad. Due to political interference India has been given one of the most inaccurate , non dependable, media as they have to support their political lobbyists. International scenario as per internet news: CHALLENGES AND POSITIVES: Can we stay Competitive? In the recent past we have seen that the Globalization 3.0 has resulted in Outsourcing and Off-shoring spreading to various other countries like China, Vietnam, Philippinesand the Eastern European countries. In the wake of such competition can we still remain competitive? The answer is pretty much yes. We know that our a Continue Reading IndiaNetzone gives idea about I T in INdia: BUT— Information Technology in India, Communication in India Information Technology in India is a key driver of the economic growth in the nation. BUT_ ALL IS NOT WELL,,,It appears to be bad. Due to political interference India has been given one of the most inaccurate , non dependable, media as they have to support their political lobbyists. International scenario as per internet news: CHALLENGES AND POSITIVES: Can we stay Competitive? In the recent past we have seen that the Globalization 3.0 has resulted in Outsourcing and Off-shoring spreading to various other countries like China, Vietnam, Philippinesand the Eastern European countries. In the wake of such competition can we still remain competitive? The answer is pretty much yes. We know that our a Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:44:51.534Z"),
    "question" : "What is the current status of Information Technology in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eaec0c817f0398f9d560"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-latest-trend-in-IT?-",
    "answer" : "Every year, Future Today Institute publishes a report on the latest tech trends and how it will affect different sectors of the economy. The number of innovations which we are seeing is evolving faster than ever. It is important for a company to pay attention to the latest tech trends for the growth and success of the company. A company should be aware of the latest innovations in IT and how to apply emerging technology trends to business development. The market research firm predicts companies worldwide will spend more than $3.5 trillion on IT in 2019. This means that there are billions of dollars at stake for the growing tech trends, things that developed within that last few years are ready to take off and become mainstream next year. Gartner and other market research firms predict the fol Continue Reading Every year, Future Today Institute publishes a report on the latest tech trends and how it will affect different sectors of the economy. The number of innovations which we are seeing is evolving faster than ever. It is important for a company to pay attention to the latest tech trends for the growth and success of the company. A company should be aware of the latest innovations in IT and how to apply emerging technology trends to business development. The market research firm predicts companies worldwide will spend more than $3.5 trillion on IT in 2019. This means that there are billions of dollars at stake for the growing tech trends, things that developed within that last few years are ready to take off and become mainstream next year. Gartner and other market research firms predict the fol Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:45:48.321Z"),
    "question" : "What is the latest trend in IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eafd0c817f0398f9d56c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-job-is-best-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Mike Yahkind Percentage wise: the majority of job opportunities fall within the software development space. The highest paid jobs are mostly either in leadership or in senior cyber security jobs, some can even reach as high as $400,000. Unfortunately for many companies, right now they are facing rising cyberattacks. Due to the rise in demand, there is a shortage of trained cyber security professionals. Fortunately for those that are in the field, the gap in the market means high paying jobs. However, pay has been rising in the search for ALL hard-to-find skills that are in demand. The upcoming mass expansion in artificial intelligence (AI) and machine learning (ML) has led to a drastic demand for these professionals. AI/ML is projected to grow by 2.3 million new jobs within the next year. The average s Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:46:05.954Z"),
    "question" : "Which job is best in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eb0e0c817f0398f9d57a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-information-technology-a-better-option-or-mechanical-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "Chiran I think I am well qualified to write answer to this question. I had this dought when I was doing my +2. Neither I know about computers nor mechanisms of a machine. I went with the wind and I had taken mechanical engineering in a good  engineering college. After 4 years of my precious life in engineering I got placed in a reputed engineering services company. I can one thing you will have to compromise in the salary,while your engineering friends are earning with 50k after 4 years u will end up earning 60%of their salary. If you are really interested either in computers and want to earn much money then better opt for IT, if you are interested in mechanical engineering theories and if your family well enough financially stable and can support for sometime irrespective of your salary then bet Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:46:22.573Z"),
    "question" : "Is information technology a better option or mechanical engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eb1f0c817f0398f9d581"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-do-I-get-started-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "I once took a 20-year old young man with ~ZERO~ IT experience (he worked at a bar) and in a few months he was employed by a technology consulting company. Here is how you do it: 1.) Find a mentor - find someone (or multiple people) in the IT world that can guide you. Meet with them on a semi-regular basis. They can give you good advice and it will start to build your network. If you are lucky you will find one that can be your mentor and can help groom you for the IT world. Invaluable are tips on everything from dress, how to dress up your resume, how to interview well, current topics, good disciplines, etc. 2.) Pick an area of IT and start ‘owning it’. By this I mean learn everything you can about it, get your hands on some equipment and start building a lab. You would be shocked at what yo Continue Reading I once took a 20-year old young man with ~ZERO~ IT experience (he worked at a bar) and in a few months he was employed by a technology consulting company. Here is how you do it: 1.) Find a mentor - find someone (or multiple people) in the IT world that can guide you. Meet with them on a semi-regular basis. They can give you good advice and it will start to build your network. If you are lucky you will find one that can be your mentor and can help groom you for the IT world. Invaluable are tips on everything from dress, how to dress up your resume, how to interview well, current topics, good disciplines, etc. 2.) Pick an area of IT and start ‘owning it’. By this I mean learn everything you can about it, get your hands on some equipment and start building a lab. You would be shocked at what yo Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:46:39.748Z"),
    "question" : "How do I get started in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eb440c817f0398f9d598"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-business-information-technology-worth-it-to-study?-",
    "answer" : "A2A Worth is a subjective criteria especially when you are talking about future job markets. Before jumping into another major that will utilize your current computer skills, it is important to understand why you feel that you will be unsuccessful. Computer Science is a blend of Mathematics, Engineering and Business, so depending on your strengths, you may want to move in those areas. It is your programming skills that is required for IT, so if you do not like (love) programming, then you should pursue a different Business major such as Accounting, Finance, Marketing, etc. You proposed direction is Business, so there are a number of different concentration in Business, some more Computer Science and some more Management. Computer Information Science is applied Computer Science in Business w Continue Reading A2A Worth is a subjective criteria especially when you are talking about future job markets. Before jumping into another major that will utilize your current computer skills, it is important to understand why you feel that you will be unsuccessful. Computer Science is a blend of Mathematics, Engineering and Business, so depending on your strengths, you may want to move in those areas. It is your programming skills that is required for IT, so if you do not like (love) programming, then you should pursue a different Business major such as Accounting, Finance, Marketing, etc. You proposed direction is Business, so there are a number of different concentration in Business, some more Computer Science and some more Management. Computer Information Science is applied Computer Science in Business w Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:47:16.319Z"),
    "question" : "Is business information technology worth it to study? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eb690c817f0398f9d5ac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-it-worth-doing-an-MBA-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Ranjeet All the specialisation are good for students, depends on your interest. At present some of the student interested in latest trend like MBA in Business analytics, Supply Chain Management, Enterprenuership Management and many more. Whether a company provides products and services online or incorporates technology into its infrastructure, professionals are needed to bridge the gap between executive leadership and technical performance. Master of Business Administration (MBA) programs in information technology provide managers with this training. MBA can open wide range of opportunities in information technology. Some of them are as follows: 1. After MBA a person can become business analyst (however even engineers from top engineering colleges can become that). 2. Technology/digital consulting is a Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:47:53.302Z"),
    "question" : "Is it worth doing an MBA in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eb8c0c817f0398f9d5c3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-advantage-and-disadvantage-of-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the advantage and disadvantage of information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:48:28.996Z"),
    "question" : "What is the advantage and disadvantage of information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eb9f0c817f0398f9d5cc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-differences-between-information-literacy-and-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the differences between information literacy and information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:48:47.092Z"),
    "question" : "What are the differences between information literacy and information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ebb30c817f0398f9d5da"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-an-Information-System?-",
    "answer" : "Your friend has started a business and puts all his vendor and customer information on 3X5 index cards and then puts the cards in a shoebox. His business becomes successful and he has shoeboxes piling up. Whenever he wants to look up a vendor or customer he has to read every card in every shoebox. One day someone asks him how many times last month customers ordered item 123456. He says he’ll have to look in every shoebox to find out. That someone then says, If you used an information system, you could type a few things on your keyboard, hit enter, and you’d know in less than a second. And if your house burned down, you’d still have all the information you need about your customers and vendors so you wouldn’t go out of business. And if someone broke into your house he could steal all your s Continue Reading Your friend has started a business and puts all his vendor and customer information on 3X5 index cards and then puts the cards in a shoebox. His business becomes successful and he has shoeboxes piling up. Whenever he wants to look up a vendor or customer he has to read every card in every shoebox. One day someone asks him how many times last month customers ordered item 123456. He says he’ll have to look in every shoebox to find out. That someone then says, If you used an information system, you could type a few things on your keyboard, hit enter, and you’d know in less than a second. And if your house burned down, you’d still have all the information you need about your customers and vendors so you wouldn’t go out of business. And if someone broke into your house he could steal all your s Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:49:07.148Z"),
    "question" : "What is an Information System? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ebc50c817f0398f9d5e6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-information-technology-and-information-communication-technology?-",
    "answer" : "In ICT, you also study about system and signals, digital signal processing, communication systems and some related hardware oriented subjects while IT is primarily software engineering with a few management oriented courses. Please visit websites of DAIICT (www.daiict.ac.in/course/b-tech-ict/) for curriculum of B.Tech (ICT) and of IIIT Allahabad (AAA @ IIIT-Allahabad) for curriculum of B.Tech (IT) (please click on Ordinance for B.Tech) and compare them. If you go through them carefully, you can understand the difference between the two. Good luck.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:49:25.488Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between information technology and information communication technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ebe80c817f0398f9d5f3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-any-risk-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is there any risk in information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:50:00.290Z"),
    "question" : "Is there any risk in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ec2f0c817f0398f9d61f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-hard-can-information-technology-be?-",
    "answer" : "Bob Hannent Information Technology can be as hard or as easy as you like. There are so many fields and sectors that the diversity gives you choices. Sometimes the courses get hard, sometimes it is only temporary, for example although I didn't study IT I did a BSc in another subject and for my first year I had to study very difficult mathematics. I failed and had to retake mathematics over the summer and I scraped through with enough points to pass. Once I passed that course I didn't have to worry again. Sometimes there are difficult parts to a course, and you need extra help to get through, but if you can work hard and push through you often find you can overcome and be successful elsewhere. If everything is too hard then you might need to change course but there are other ways of working that perhaps  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:51:11.845Z"),
    "question" : "How hard can information technology be? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ec410c817f0398f9d629"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-information-technology-being-used-in-education?-",
    "answer" : "1. Digital Simulations And Models Digital simulations and models can help teachers more tangibly and clearly explain difficult concepts and can help students who are visual or tactile learners better understand the concepts. 2. You Can Now Finish a Degree Online For those that work all day and can’t go to class in person, online education has been a stunning arrangement. From the ivy leagues to junior college, many different types of institutions offer online courses, certifications, and degrees. 3. Improved Communication Ineffective correspondence among teachers and students can be a hindrance to learning and education. Technology can change the classroom into a network where teachers post assignments progressively, and students can ask questions more easily–of teachers and of their peers–and  Continue Reading 1. Digital Simulations And Models Digital simulations and models can help teachers more tangibly and clearly explain difficult concepts and can help students who are visual or tactile learners better understand the concepts. 2. You Can Now Finish a Degree Online For those that work all day and can’t go to class in person, online education has been a stunning arrangement. From the ivy leagues to junior college, many different types of institutions offer online courses, certifications, and degrees. 3. Improved Communication Ineffective correspondence among teachers and students can be a hindrance to learning and education. Technology can change the classroom into a network where teachers post assignments progressively, and students can ask questions more easily–of teachers and of their peers–and  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:51:29.504Z"),
    "question" : "How is information technology being used in education? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ec670c817f0398f9d63e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-role-of-information-technology-in-the-environment-and-human-health?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the role of information technology in the environment and human health?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:52:07.505Z"),
    "question" : "What is the role of information technology in the environment and human health? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ec790c817f0398f9d656"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-colleges-in-India-for-a-MBA-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Hi, MBA IN IT (INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY), is a master’s degree in business administration, which attracts people from a wide range of academic disciplines. The MBA designation originated in the United States, emerging from the late 19th century as the country industrialized and companies sought out scientific approaches to management. MBA in IT Management offers the advanced technical and business knowledge to assemble multifaceted technology and business challenges. It focuses on IT and use of management skills to develop the usage and appropriation of IT. It will take you from junior to upper level IT Management positions. You will become an advanced IT Manager with ability and information that keep you ahead. An MBA in IT Management program covers subjects such as computer hardware, compute Continue Reading Continue Reading Vishag Vh",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:52:25.147Z"),
    "question" : "What are the top colleges in India for a MBA in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ecc30c817f0398f9d67e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-there-a-future-for-information-technology-in-India?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is there a future for information technology in India?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:53:39.611Z"),
    "question" : "Is there a future for information technology in India? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ece70c817f0398f9d696"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-various-sectors-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Aditya Konarde, Red Hat Certified System Administrator, Computer Engineering Student.Answered 5 years ago · Author has 57 answers and 115.2K answer viewsWhat are the various sectors in information technology? Aditya Konarde Being a CSE student, I have come across these major domains as of now: Software Development : Work for developing software products, mobile apps, all sorts of maintenance of software etc.System Administration : Job of a system admin is to manage the IT infrastructure. System admin is responsible for the uptime of the servers and applying essential updates, handling requirements of employees related to software.Network Administration : Managing the network infrastructure of company, Implementing policies regarding firewalls, routing etc.Hardware Engineering : A hardware engineer typically deals with the hardware in the company. It ranges from managing and troubleshooting systems, routers, and any other hardware you can think ofTech Support : Talking to the clients and troubleshooting issues,Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:54:15.976Z"),
    "question" : "What are the various sectors in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ecf90c817f0398f9d69e"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-I-prepare-for-better-job-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Lee Peyton This question lacks specifics, but I will answer the two different ways I see it being interpreted.   IT is a career that if you do not love technology and how it functions you are going to have a bad time. There are other ways to make money.  Getting a “Good job in IT”:  If you are currently working in IT but you hate your surroundings or you are looking for more income with creature comforts skip the longer part.   Specialize, cert up, build your resume and keep your LinkedIn updated. If you do not like the people you are working with, change it. If you feel you are not being paid fairly, change it. If you have done your part in experience building the best you can with the job or jobs you have while keeping your knowledge fresh the rest is just a process. Sometimes experience bu Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:54:33.462Z"),
    "question" : "How can I prepare for better job in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ed0d0c817f0398f9d6b1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-websites-to-follow-the-latest-technologies-and-developments-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Abhishek Sharma There are a lot of websites through which you can get updated regarding tech and life hacks. But there’s a new website which regularly updates useful content. The matter of surprise is that being amateur, this website comes on the top pages of search engines such as Google. Some of its posts are also on the first page of Google. You can update yourself regarding latest tech feeds, life hacks and health issues. Here’s a link to the website: BrainDine | Get yourself updated with the latest tech news, life hacks and brain feeds...",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:54:53.727Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best websites to follow the latest technologies and developments in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ed330c817f0398f9d6cb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-would-be-a-title-for-a-thesis-that-suits-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Everything Equifax has done wrong and what lessons to learn from it. The Office of Personnel Management breach and what went wrong. Maybe cover the story of how it was accidentally discovered. The Awan brothers hacking the DNC from the inside and how the insider threat is the biggest threat, and you can parallel it to Wikileaks and Mr. Manning. You can also discuss solutions like the tools being implemented to try to prevent data leaks. Cloud computing moving from software as a service to infrastructure as a service and beyond. The technological development for the developing world like Youtube for India that runs on 2G networks and low grade “smart” phones. The Singularity as a religion, that there is no God but they want to invent an all knowing, all seeing, all powerful artificial intelligen Continue Reading Everything Equifax has done wrong and what lessons to learn from it. The Office of Personnel Management breach and what went wrong. Maybe cover the story of how it was accidentally discovered. The Awan brothers hacking the DNC from the inside and how the insider threat is the biggest threat, and you can parallel it to Wikileaks and Mr. Manning. You can also discuss solutions like the tools being implemented to try to prevent data leaks. Cloud computing moving from software as a service to infrastructure as a service and beyond. The technological development for the developing world like Youtube for India that runs on 2G networks and low grade “smart” phones. The Singularity as a religion, that there is no God but they want to invent an all knowing, all seeing, all powerful artificial intelligen Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:55:31.228Z"),
    "question" : "What would be a title for a thesis that suits in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ed460c817f0398f9d6e0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-meant-by-information-technology?-How-has-it-helped-in-promotion-of-export-of-service-of-India?-",
    "answer" : "Nitish BhardwajAnswered 7 months ago · Author has 580 answers and 182.5K answer viewsWhat is information technology? Nitish Bhardwaj Information technology (IT) is the use of computers to store, retrieve, transmit, and manipulate data or information. Computers are generally used in the context of business operations instead of personal or entertainment technologies. IT is seen as a subset of information and communication technology (ICT).Information technology (IT) is the use of any computer, storage, network, and other physical devices, infrastructure, and processes to create, process, store, protect, and exchange all forms of electronic data. IT is generally used in the context of business operations rather than personal or entertainment technologies. Commercial use of computers includes computer technology and telephony.It includes several layers of physical equipment (hardware), virtualization and administration or Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:55:50.309Z"),
    "question" : "What is information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ed580c817f0398f9d6ec"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-interesting-thesis-topics-about-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Tamara Wilhite The rise of influencers and the parallel growth of purchased likes, followers and subscribers to look like you have influence. The impact of Google’s censorship on businesses and related lawsuits The shift in SEO toward conversational queries because of information appliances and the influx of brand mentions in streaming media so that people cannot avoid the ad via traditional add blockers. The growth of outrage culture and social media digital hate mobs, enabled by social media’s ability to tap into masses of bored people eager to bully strangers when given moral cover and the lack of constraint because you have to live with/around the person later. Jon Ronson’s book “So you’ve been publicly shamed” and TED Talk on that same subject is a good first look at this. Rodel James Tamayo",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:56:08.008Z"),
    "question" : "What are interesting thesis topics about information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ed7d0c817f0398f9d702"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Should-I-study-computer-science-or-information-systems?-",
    "answer" : "Levi Heidrick It comes down to many things choosing what to study in college. AS someone who is currently studying information technology I will give some hopefully helpful advice.  I thought long and hard about Comp SCI or IT and I chose IT for various reasons. At my university both degrees are offered through the school of engineering, so either way you get an engineering degree. Both degrees require courses in discrete mathematics, statistics and physics. Plus data structures and algorithms as well as other various programming courses including databases,  operating systems and software engineering. But information technology is broader as it includes courses in security and managing systems, servers and systems administration. Comp SCI parts ways at that point because instead of those aforementioned  Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:56:45.658Z"),
    "question" : "Should I study computer science or information systems? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ed920c817f0398f9d714"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-and-currently-hot-research-topics-in-the-field-of-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Ahmad Alhaji Inuwa I'm not entirely sure if the following topics will fall under 'hot research topics', however I reviewed them all trying to select a topic for my final year project - BSc IT. So here you go: Multi-hop wireless sensor networks for smart cities (Energy-efficiency is a key design criterion for these sensor networks, to produce a new generation of smarter, more proactive, information services. This new technology should automatically monitor the quality of our environments.)Security analytics: methodology and tools (The overall research project aims to propose novel architectures, methodologies and tools to guarantee security in critical Internet-based infrastructures.)Knowledge-enabled Access of SMEs to the Electronic Market (Aim is for small companies acting in different countries and sectContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:57:06.791Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best and currently hot research topics in the field of Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034edaa0c817f0398f9d727"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-a-BS-in-computer-science-vs-a-BS-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "They have a lot of similarities, particularly in the basic foundation and some applications -- our first-year subjects are the same. In fact, CS majors take some IT subjects and IT majors take some CS subjects. However, the ultimate focus of the programs are different. CS is more inclined towards the more mathematical and software side of the field, solving the problems in artificial intelligence, operating systems, programming languages. On the other hand, IT is more inclined towards the business and people side of the field, like databases, project management, quality assurance. The computer engineering program has both CS and IT subjects, but the ultimate focus is hardware.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:57:30.076Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between a BS in computer science vs a BS in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034edc00c817f0398f9d736"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-blockchain-technologies-be-applied-to-patent-information?-",
    "answer" : "Among the latest innovation in computer technology, the most exciting is the use of Blockchain Technology. It is only a decade old that began with Satoshi Nakamoto and his invention, a cryptocurrency known as Bitcoin. Blockchain is known as a distributed electronic ledger. Instead of storing one or two copies of a record, storing it on multiple computers is safer. Every time a participant alters the ledger, the modifications are downloaded to every other node. It prevents hacking, and the backbone of the system is known as a Blockchain. What are its applications? Digital Identity – If X needs to transfer ownership of an asset to Y, then all he needs to do is provide the key to a block of assets (most often cryptocurrency). No real transaction needs to happen except for an alphanumeric string to  Continue Reading Among the latest innovation in computer technology, the most exciting is the use of Blockchain Technology. It is only a decade old that began with Satoshi Nakamoto and his invention, a cryptocurrency known as Bitcoin. Blockchain is known as a distributed electronic ledger. Instead of storing one or two copies of a record, storing it on multiple computers is safer. Every time a participant alters the ledger, the modifications are downloaded to every other node. It prevents hacking, and the backbone of the system is known as a Blockchain. What are its applications? Digital Identity – If X needs to transfer ownership of an asset to Y, then all he needs to do is provide the key to a block of assets (most often cryptocurrency). No real transaction needs to happen except for an alphanumeric string to  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:57:52.930Z"),
    "question" : "How can blockchain technologies be applied to patent information? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034edd70c817f0398f9d74a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-interesting-topics-for-research-in-the-field-of-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Check this web page for research topics of IT KAIST School of Computing, 카이스트 전산학부 - 컴퓨터공학과 컴퓨터과학(Computer Science & Engineering)을 교육하고 연구하는 국내 최대 규모의 전산학부 The following is a good summary of areas Algorithms and BioinformaticsComputer Architecture and Real Time SystemsDatabase and Data MiningDependable, Reliable and Autonomic ComputingDistributed and Parallel Systems & AlgorithmsDSP/Image Processing/Pattern Recognition/MultimediaEmbedded System and SoftwareGame and Software EngineeringGeographical Information Systems/ Global Navigation Satellite Systems (GIS/GNSS)Grid and Scalable ComputingIntelligent Information & Database SystemsIT policy and Business ManagementMobile and Ubiquitous ComputingModeling and SimulationMultimedia Systems and ServicesNetworking and CommunicationsParallel and DistContinue Reading Check this web page for research topics of IT KAIST School of Computing, 카이스트 전산학부 - 컴퓨터공학과 컴퓨터과학(Computer Science & Engineering)을 교육하고 연구하는 국내 최대 규모의 전산학부 The following is a good summary of areas Algorithms and BioinformaticsComputer Architecture and Real Time SystemsDatabase and Data MiningDependable, Reliable and Autonomic ComputingDistributed and Parallel Systems & AlgorithmsDSP/Image Processing/Pattern Recognition/MultimediaEmbedded System and SoftwareGame and Software EngineeringGeographical Information Systems/ Global Navigation Satellite Systems (GIS/GNSS)Grid and Scalable ComputingIntelligent Information & Database SystemsIT policy and Business ManagementMobile and Ubiquitous ComputingModeling and SimulationMultimedia Systems and ServicesNetworking and CommunicationsParallel and DistContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:58:15.689Z"),
    "question" : "What are some interesting topics for research in the field of information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034edec0c817f0398f9d752"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-city-to-earn-in-Information-technology-field?-",
    "answer" : "Actually if you are really good in your field then it doesn't matters in which city you reside or you work in. However the best city to work if in it sector then it is Bangalore as because of three main reasons:- 1.Good climate, helpful people and good inter connectivity between places. 2. Low cost Paying guest accommodations you could save a lot of money on living can even get a pg near to your work place and can save a lot of money on travelling also. 3. The most important one a lot of major companies and startups are there in the city where you can work to get a better life and earnings. Other cities after Bangalore you could work in are Gurugram before known as gurgaon if can manage with Tamil then Chennai is a better option also.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:58:36.905Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best city to earn in Information technology field? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034edff0c817f0398f9d760"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-coding-present-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Yes That said, I assume English is not your first language (no disrespect intended) because, as written, your question is almost meaningless. I hope the following touches on things you already know to better answer your question. “Information Technology” (IT), in common usage, relates to computers and their use in processing data (also known as information). IT used to be called “Data Processing\". Any computer, processing any kind of data, needs programming of some sort. The types of program range from “operating systems\" (OS) that magage the use of computer hardware, to “applications” (also known as “apps\") that perform functions useful to humans, to tools and utilities to manipulate various things in the IT environment. Likewise, the types of programming and the tools used vary widely. For Continue Reading Yes That said, I assume English is not your first language (no disrespect intended) because, as written, your question is almost meaningless. I hope the following touches on things you already know to better answer your question. “Information Technology” (IT), in common usage, relates to computers and their use in processing data (also known as information). IT used to be called “Data Processing\". Any computer, processing any kind of data, needs programming of some sort. The types of program range from “operating systems\" (OS) that magage the use of computer hardware, to “applications” (also known as “apps\") that perform functions useful to humans, to tools and utilities to manipulate various things in the IT environment. Likewise, the types of programming and the tools used vary widely. For Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:58:55.849Z"),
    "question" : "Is coding present in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ee130c817f0398f9d774"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-difference-between-information-science-and-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the difference between information science and information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T11:59:15.566Z"),
    "question" : "What is the difference between information science and information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ee4e0c817f0398f9d798"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-First-year-syllabus-of-engineering-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Vivek Iyer Mumbai University syllabus for First year engineering stands the same for all branches. SEMESTER 1: Theory Subjects— 1)Applied Mathematics 1 2)Applied Physics 1 3)Applied Chemistry 1 4)Engineering Mechanics 5)Basics of Electrical and Electronics. 6)Environmental Studies Practical Subjects— 1)Applied Physics 2)Applied Chemistry 3)Engineering Mechanics 4)Basics of Electrical and Electronics. Tutorial Subjects— 1)Applied Mathematics 1 SEMESTER 2: Theory Subjects— 1)Applied Mathematics 2 2)Applied Physics 2 3)Applied Chemistry 2 4)Engineering Drawing 5)Structured Programming Approach 6)Communication Skills Practical Subjects— 1)Applied Physics 2)Applied Chemistry 3)Autocad 4)C Programming. Tutorial Subjects— 1)Applied Mathematics 2 ALL THE BEST :) Vivek Iyer, 3rd Year Engg IT, SIES GRADUATE SCHOOL OF TECHNOLOGY, NAVI MUMBAI Naveen Gupta",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:00:14.486Z"),
    "question" : "What is First year syllabus of engineering in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ee620c817f0398f9d7a1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-five-importances-of-information-and-communication-technology?-",
    "answer" : "The five importance of IT and communication is. business:- the IT and communication systems helping many businesses. we can see even a street food uncle have a UPI payment system just because of IT.education:- the education system is nowadays are very digital and available everywhere just because of IT. for example, byjus, Chegg, unacademy, udemy, Coursera, edx,mva etc are using IT and COMM we can LEARN from any teacher , any university, anytime anywhere, in the world because of this technologyspace and aeronautical engineering:- it is useful for research on space . also useful during communication or tracking aircraft and spacecraft for example Aeroplane, Stalite, drones etc.daily life:- Due to IT and COMM our life is easier nowadays we can reach anywhere in this world or contact anyone foContinue Reading The five importance of IT and communication is. business:- the IT and communication systems helping many businesses. we can see even a street food uncle have a UPI payment system just because of IT.education:- the education system is nowadays are very digital and available everywhere just because of IT. for example, byjus, Chegg, unacademy, udemy, Coursera, edx,mva etc are using IT and COMM we can LEARN from any teacher , any university, anytime anywhere, in the world because of this technologyspace and aeronautical engineering:- it is useful for research on space . also useful during communication or tracking aircraft and spacecraft for example Aeroplane, Stalite, drones etc.daily life:- Due to IT and COMM our life is easier nowadays we can reach anywhere in this world or contact anyone foContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:00:34.338Z"),
    "question" : "What are the five importances of information and communication technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ee770c817f0398f9d7b0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-are-there-no-unions-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "I have worked in both in a highly unionized environment and in IT, though not at the same time. My formal education also included a course on the history of Labor organization. These are some of the reasons why you don't see unions in IT:  As unpleasant as some IT work can be, there have been no widespread instances of overt worker abuse to act as a catalyst for unionization.IT workers are generally more mobile than those in the traditionally unionized industries, both in the sense that IT systems are relatively similar globally and in the sense that there is still a relatively high demand for them across the board.On the flip side, IT workers build up specialized knowledge within organizations over time and are often expensive to replace. When this happens, they tend to be chained to their pContinue Reading I have worked in both in a highly unionized environment and in IT, though not at the same time. My formal education also included a course on the history of Labor organization. These are some of the reasons why you don't see unions in IT:  As unpleasant as some IT work can be, there have been no widespread instances of overt worker abuse to act as a catalyst for unionization.IT workers are generally more mobile than those in the traditionally unionized industries, both in the sense that IT systems are relatively similar globally and in the sense that there is still a relatively high demand for them across the board.On the flip side, IT workers build up specialized knowledge within organizations over time and are often expensive to replace. When this happens, they tend to be chained to their pContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:00:55.606Z"),
    "question" : "Why are there no unions in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ee8b0c817f0398f9d7c4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-should-I-do-after-btech-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Thanks for A2A. This answer should help you Shubham Dave's answer to What are the career options after B.tech in Information Technology? Is it the end if I am not too much interested in coding or development? or Shubham Dave's answer to I am pursuing my diploma in Information technology. What should I do after that? Essentially after removing B.Tech from all options :) Now there could be one other question that arises from these answers, what if I want to land a job or something related to job ? Shubham Dave's answer to How can I get a job just after completing my B.Tech? Shubham Dave's answer to Which job should I choose to become billionaire as I'm pursuing IT engineering? Both of these answers will help you in getting something that you would want from a job. I hope I answered you query sufficien Continue Reading Thanks for A2A. This answer should help you Shubham Dave's answer to What are the career options after B.tech in Information Technology? Is it the end if I am not too much interested in coding or development? or Shubham Dave's answer to I am pursuing my diploma in Information technology. What should I do after that? Essentially after removing B.Tech from all options :) Now there could be one other question that arises from these answers, what if I want to land a job or something related to job ? Shubham Dave's answer to How can I get a job just after completing my B.Tech? Shubham Dave's answer to Which job should I choose to become billionaire as I'm pursuing IT engineering? Both of these answers will help you in getting something that you would want from a job. I hope I answered you query sufficien Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:01:15.596Z"),
    "question" : "What should I do after btech in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ee9e0c817f0398f9d7cb"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Are-computer-technology-and-information-technology-the-same?-",
    "answer" : "Pretty much. But the title “Computer Technology” is a bit strange. It’s not something you see often in the world of computers. Do You Mean Something Else? Do you mean “computer sciences” and “internet technology”? Because there are some slight difference in both – even though they share much in common. I’ll explain both below. This should give you an idea on what to expect if you’re studying each. What IT is. IT is all about working with databases and networks. It’s involved shuffling and organizing data on systems. It’s what businesses want in employees that manage logistics, etc. And there’s a little hardware involved too. So it’s not as computer-focused as “computer sciences” (I’ll get to that in a minute). Examples. You have tech support. That’s a common job title for IT graduates. And they’re the  Continue Reading Pretty much. But the title “Computer Technology” is a bit strange. It’s not something you see often in the world of computers. Do You Mean Something Else? Do you mean “computer sciences” and “internet technology”? Because there are some slight difference in both – even though they share much in common. I’ll explain both below. This should give you an idea on what to expect if you’re studying each. What IT is. IT is all about working with databases and networks. It’s involved shuffling and organizing data on systems. It’s what businesses want in employees that manage logistics, etc. And there’s a little hardware involved too. So it’s not as computer-focused as “computer sciences” (I’ll get to that in a minute). Examples. You have tech support. That’s a common job title for IT graduates. And they’re the  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:01:34.767Z"),
    "question" : "Are computer technology and information technology the same? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034eeda0c817f0398f9d7ff"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-information-communication-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Technology that enables you to create, modify and view information, and technology that enables people and \"things\" to communicate. A spreadsheet [on a computer ] is an example of the first. Email is an example of the second. At one time , spreadsheets were on paper(!). At one time, people in large organisations would send each other [paper] memos; you would get internal mail once or twice a day. The rest of the time, you were free to actually work!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:02:34.120Z"),
    "question" : "What is information communication technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef040c817f0398f9d821"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-project-ideas-for-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are project ideas for information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:03:16.829Z"),
    "question" : "What are project ideas for information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef180c817f0398f9d829"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-meant-by-technologies-of-globalisation?-",
    "answer" : "Technological Globalization Technological globalization is speeded in large part by technological diffusion, the spread of technology across borders. In the last two decades, there has been rapid improvement in the spread of technology to peripheral and semi-peripheral nations, and a 2008 World Bank report discusses both the benefits and ongoing challenges of this diffusion. In general, the report found that technological progress and economic growth rates were linked, and that the rise in technological progress has helped improve the situations of many living in absolute poverty (World Bank 2008). The report recognizes that rural and low-tech products such as corn can benefit from new technological innovations, and that, conversely, technologies like mobile banking can aid those whose rura Continue Reading Technological Globalization Technological globalization is speeded in large part by technological diffusion, the spread of technology across borders. In the last two decades, there has been rapid improvement in the spread of technology to peripheral and semi-peripheral nations, and a 2008 World Bank report discusses both the benefits and ongoing challenges of this diffusion. In general, the report found that technological progress and economic growth rates were linked, and that the rise in technological progress has helped improve the situations of many living in absolute poverty (World Bank 2008). The report recognizes that rural and low-tech products such as corn can benefit from new technological innovations, and that, conversely, technologies like mobile banking can aid those whose rura Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:03:36.928Z"),
    "question" : "What is meant by technologies of globalisation? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef2e0c817f0398f9d83b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-different-fields-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Information technology – often shortened to just IT – is a buzz phrase you’ve probably heard ad nauseum if you happen to work with IT personnel or went to school for anything related to computers. IT workers are highly specialized in their field, which is probably why they’re often just called “IT nerds.” They like what they do and understand it inside and out. IT workers are also essential to just about every modern business model. If a company relies on phones and emails, chances are that there’s an IT professional behind it all making sure the cogs in the machine function properly. So what’s the real benefit of being the behind-the-scenes technological lifeblood of a company? Excellent pay is your reward, more often than not. As the economy finds its footing and more jobs open up, expect Continue Reading Information technology – often shortened to just IT – is a buzz phrase you’ve probably heard ad nauseum if you happen to work with IT personnel or went to school for anything related to computers. IT workers are highly specialized in their field, which is probably why they’re often just called “IT nerds.” They like what they do and understand it inside and out. IT workers are also essential to just about every modern business model. If a company relies on phones and emails, chances are that there’s an IT professional behind it all making sure the cogs in the machine function properly. So what’s the real benefit of being the behind-the-scenes technological lifeblood of a company? Excellent pay is your reward, more often than not. As the economy finds its footing and more jobs open up, expect Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:03:58.975Z"),
    "question" : "What are the different fields in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef440c817f0398f9d851"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-32-too-old-to-return-to-school-for-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Definitely not! I am 32 and started out as a Web Dev 1 year ago. I have 2 young children and have been working from home to try and get my skills up to any kind of employable level. By the way it looks like I have a job starting Jan 1st 2015. It took over a year but I have learnt so much and it was definitely worth it. This is what I can advise... take from it what you will: 1) Have some sort of plan (but expect it to deviate)You will need some kind of plan in order to focus your efforts. However with my experience you discover so much as you go along that your plans will inevitably change. Obviously you don't want to constantly jump from idea to idea but also you don't want to get stuck in a place where it then becomes a chore. 2) Be disciplined with your timeI heard this advise on a docu Continue Reading Definitely not! I am 32 and started out as a Web Dev 1 year ago. I have 2 young children and have been working from home to try and get my skills up to any kind of employable level. By the way it looks like I have a job starting Jan 1st 2015. It took over a year but I have learnt so much and it was definitely worth it. This is what I can advise... take from it what you will: 1) Have some sort of plan (but expect it to deviate)You will need some kind of plan in order to focus your efforts. However with my experience you discover so much as you go along that your plans will inevitably change. Obviously you don't want to constantly jump from idea to idea but also you don't want to get stuck in a place where it then becomes a chore. 2) Be disciplined with your timeI heard this advise on a docu Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:04:20.545Z"),
    "question" : "Is 32 too old to return to school for information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef6d0c817f0398f9d865"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-cheapest-universities-in-Australia-for-studying-Information-technology-for-international-students?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the cheapest universities in Australia for studying Information technology for international students?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:05:01.720Z"),
    "question" : "What are the cheapest universities in Australia for studying Information technology for international students? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef800c817f0398f9d87b"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-information-technology-a-good-choice-of-branch?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Is information technology a good choice of branch?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:05:20.028Z"),
    "question" : "Is information technology a good choice of branch? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 18 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034ef920c817f0398f9d882"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-a-BSc-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Michelle Carlos A Bachelor of Science in Information Technology degree program typically takes three to four years depending on the country. This degree is primarily focused on subjects such as software, databases, and networking. In general, computer science degrees tend to focus on the mathematical and theoretical foundations of computing rather than emphasizing specific technologies. The degree is a Bachelor of Science degree with institutions conferring degrees in the fields of information technology and related fields. This degree is awarded for completing a program of study in the field of software development, software testing, software engineering, web design, databases, programming, and computer networking and computer systems. Adam Morris",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:05:38.812Z"),
    "question" : "What is a BSc in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 19 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034efa70c817f0398f9d890"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-country-do-you-think-would-be-best-for-studying-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Hi!! Countries like India,USA,UK,Australia. But it’s upto you. Country doesn’t matter if you’re not attentive in your studies. if you really want to be an Engineer you can be in your home country too. Yanz Lee",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:05:59.363Z"),
    "question" : "Which country do you think would be best for studying information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 20 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034efb90c817f0398f9d8a3"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-most-important-information-technology-problems-in-the-world?-",
    "answer" : "I've worked in IT and Web/Internet fields for about 20 years, and I would say that personally what I've seen is the lack of adoption of current/updated systems.   Many companies are still running outdated code, done by developers long gone and that can't be supported on anything but outdated systems like NT4).    Also many companies are slow to upgrade and/or adopt newer technology.   In many cases, MIS management in companies will use arguments like \"Let's wait until the bugs are worked out before upgrading,\" even though this argument is outmoded and incorrect for a lot of reasons - not the least of which being that, say, a Windows 2012 R2 server is built on better and more secure technology than a full patched and tested Windows 2003 or Windows 2008 R2 server. Also security at most compan Continue Reading I've worked in IT and Web/Internet fields for about 20 years, and I would say that personally what I've seen is the lack of adoption of current/updated systems.   Many companies are still running outdated code, done by developers long gone and that can't be supported on anything but outdated systems like NT4).    Also many companies are slow to upgrade and/or adopt newer technology.   In many cases, MIS management in companies will use arguments like \"Let's wait until the bugs are worked out before upgrading,\" even though this argument is outmoded and incorrect for a lot of reasons - not the least of which being that, say, a Windows 2012 R2 server is built on better and more secure technology than a full patched and tested Windows 2003 or Windows 2008 R2 server. Also security at most compan Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:06:17.436Z"),
    "question" : "What are the most important information technology problems in the world? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 21 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034efcf0c817f0398f9d8ae"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-it-like-studying-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Are you still looking at study options? Choosing a career path can be stressful and overwhelming. To find what your perfect career choice would be you should evaluate yourself and determined what you truly enjoy doing. We’re in the 21st century and today everything’s about technology. It’s seen in almost every aspect of modern life. If you enjoy technology and specifically keeping up with the latest advances in the field of information technology, you might want to turn your hobby into a career. In today’s society, information is paramount and information technology (IT) influences all kinds of human activity. Benefits of technology include increased productivity in many work-related and personal tasks. Information technology jobs fall within the full spectrum of computer technology and busi Continue Reading Are you still looking at study options? Choosing a career path can be stressful and overwhelming. To find what your perfect career choice would be you should evaluate yourself and determined what you truly enjoy doing. We’re in the 21st century and today everything’s about technology. It’s seen in almost every aspect of modern life. If you enjoy technology and specifically keeping up with the latest advances in the field of information technology, you might want to turn your hobby into a career. In today’s society, information is paramount and information technology (IT) influences all kinds of human activity. Benefits of technology include increased productivity in many work-related and personal tasks. Information technology jobs fall within the full spectrum of computer technology and busi Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:06:39.105Z"),
    "question" : "What is it like studying information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 22 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f0040c817f0398f9d8d7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-latest-technology-in-the-VLSI-field?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What is the latest technology in the VLSI field?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:07:32.720Z"),
    "question" : "What is the latest technology in the VLSI field? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 23 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f0160c817f0398f9d8e4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-educational-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Educational technology; defined as a platform to enhance learning through different digital tools, strives to improve pedagogical transactions anywhere, anytime. A crucial component of ET is its evolving nature, enabling children to learn better and faster. Now let me exemplify this and share my experience in the Indian context and how they have evolved in the recent years and what may the future look like? First came the basic Windows Computers or desktop PC’s which stored information on floppy drives. Typically we were taught calculations, typing and a few basic languages and thus preparing us to take on the real world challenges. Since then education technology has come a long way, and its progress indeed amazes me. This is what a computer used to look like, during our ET sessions in our Continue Reading Educational technology; defined as a platform to enhance learning through different digital tools, strives to improve pedagogical transactions anywhere, anytime. A crucial component of ET is its evolving nature, enabling children to learn better and faster. Now let me exemplify this and share my experience in the Indian context and how they have evolved in the recent years and what may the future look like? First came the basic Windows Computers or desktop PC’s which stored information on floppy drives. Typically we were taught calculations, typing and a few basic languages and thus preparing us to take on the real world challenges. Since then education technology has come a long way, and its progress indeed amazes me. This is what a computer used to look like, during our ET sessions in our Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:07:50.664Z"),
    "question" : "What is educational technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 24 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f0290c817f0398f9d8f4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-is-computer-technology-called-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Why is computer technology called information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:08:09.926Z"),
    "question" : "Why is computer technology called information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 25 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f03b0c817f0398f9d90a"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-impacts-of-Information-Technology-services-in-the-healthcare-industry?-",
    "answer" : "Austin Ahamba Time has really elapsed and day by day we see the emergence of new technologies into different industries and the healthcare sector has not been left out. Several aspects of the Healthcare Industry have been impacted by Information Technology - patient care, maintaining customer satisfaction and most recently in driving marketing results. Talking about driving marketing results, branding and also maintaining customer satisfaction - the introduction of a tech like call tracking has helped improve performances across these sectors of the Healthcare Industry. However one thing to consider while doing that, is the vitality and privacy of Healthcare information. These information are most times very private and collecting medical information (data) over the phone in order to increase marketing p Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:08:27.190Z"),
    "question" : "What are the impacts of Information Technology services in the healthcare industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 26 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f1790c817f0398f9d9e0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-subjects-should-I-take-in-school-to-study-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What subjects should I take in school to study Information Technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:13:45.478Z"),
    "question" : "What subjects should I take in school to study Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 27 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f1b00c817f0398f9da08"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-upcoming-Java-technologies-which-will-shock-the-information-technology-field-in-the-future?-",
    "answer" : "Renjith Narayanan",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:14:40.058Z"),
    "question" : "What are the upcoming Java technologies which will shock the information technology field in the future? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 28 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f1c70c817f0398f9da18"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Can-I-become-a-software-engineer-with-a-Information-Technology-degree?-",
    "answer" : "The answer is a resounding, 100%, yes. How do I know? Well, the main reason is that I have no degree at all, and I've had a going on 25yr career, in all manner of IT, computer science, and software development roles. I have been a network admin. I have been a software developer. I have been an “internet/web” developer. I have been an IT manager. I have been a program manager, a project manager, a software development manager, a lead developer, an Engineering & Technology Manager, a Director of Systems Management (otherwise known as Director of Technology), and way way back starting my career (far enough back I dont even bother keeping them on my resume or LinkedIn profiles) I was even a help desk tech for a major corporation and a network tech who built pcs, servers, and networks. So, my qu Continue Reading The answer is a resounding, 100%, yes. How do I know? Well, the main reason is that I have no degree at all, and I've had a going on 25yr career, in all manner of IT, computer science, and software development roles. I have been a network admin. I have been a software developer. I have been an “internet/web” developer. I have been an IT manager. I have been a program manager, a project manager, a software development manager, a lead developer, an Engineering & Technology Manager, a Director of Systems Management (otherwise known as Director of Technology), and way way back starting my career (far enough back I dont even bother keeping them on my resume or LinkedIn profiles) I was even a help desk tech for a major corporation and a network tech who built pcs, servers, and networks. So, my qu Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:15:03.917Z"),
    "question" : "Can I become a software engineer with a Information Technology degree? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 29 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f1fb0c817f0398f9da3c"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-university-is-good-for-information-technology-in-Canada?-",
    "answer" : "It depends on your career goals mostly, and the rate of graduates who end up employed and able to pay off their debts in their field of choice. Unfortunately, many universities and colleges in Canada are rated not by these factors but on silly, trivial things such as how good the night-life is or how easy it is to “make friends”. I’m totally serious. Pick up any Dalhousie University brochure and you’ll see mostly promises of great pubs and bars, a huge gymnasium and lots of social interaction - very little, if anything, discussing career opportunities or the actual education involved behind obtaining a degree there. The same could be said for many post-secondary schools in North America, from two-year community colleges to Ivy League schools. I would recommend a place with low residence co Continue Reading It depends on your career goals mostly, and the rate of graduates who end up employed and able to pay off their debts in their field of choice. Unfortunately, many universities and colleges in Canada are rated not by these factors but on silly, trivial things such as how good the night-life is or how easy it is to “make friends”. I’m totally serious. Pick up any Dalhousie University brochure and you’ll see mostly promises of great pubs and bars, a huge gymnasium and lots of social interaction - very little, if anything, discussing career opportunities or the actual education involved behind obtaining a degree there. The same could be said for many post-secondary schools in North America, from two-year community colleges to Ivy League schools. I would recommend a place with low residence co Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:15:55.100Z"),
    "question" : "Which university is good for information technology in Canada? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 30 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2100c817f0398f9da52"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-role-of-information-technology-for-a-career?-",
    "answer" : "Presumably someone can structure this as a goal and IT can converge on solutions. In the past it had tended to obsolete positions going forward like burning the bridges. There is a question of limits as usual. People want to know how to identify niches, or marketing, and how to exploit methods, or innovation, so these are combined.  Though it was stereotyped as a geekdom, it will be interesting to see what new personality types will be like since they are not all psychopaths, and will explore creativity and empathy. There is a notion of motivation, e.g. if they have a strong idea then find a way to make it happen in contrast to those who liked to take orders instead such as civil servants. This may be what startups require. Then there is an issue if academics is necessary and sufficient from Continue Reading Presumably someone can structure this as a goal and IT can converge on solutions. In the past it had tended to obsolete positions going forward like burning the bridges. There is a question of limits as usual. People want to know how to identify niches, or marketing, and how to exploit methods, or innovation, so these are combined.  Though it was stereotyped as a geekdom, it will be interesting to see what new personality types will be like since they are not all psychopaths, and will explore creativity and empathy. There is a notion of motivation, e.g. if they have a strong idea then find a way to make it happen in contrast to those who liked to take orders instead such as civil servants. This may be what startups require. Then there is an issue if academics is necessary and sufficient from Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:16:16.842Z"),
    "question" : "What is role of information technology for a career? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 31 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2350c817f0398f9da68"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-career-scope-of-Masters-in-Information-Technology-in-Australia?-",
    "answer" : "Shilpa W, lives in AustraliaAnswered 1 year ago · Author has 142 answers and 202.4K answer viewsWhat is the career scope of Masters in Information Technology in Australia? Shilpa W Information technology – often shortened to just IT – is a buzz phrase you’ve probably heard ad nauseum if you happen to work with IT personnel or went to school for anything related to computers. When it comes to international education, Career in Australia certainly is among the top spot takers. And there are good enough reasons for it. Most of the students come from different corners of the world to explore the best study opportunity in the land down under. Information Technology in Australia The tech sector in Australia is booming at a good rate. The rapid rise in the need for automation and the ease with which people are adapting to technology has a big impact on the needs of Technology Specialists. With the advent of newer technology comes the need for maintenance, security and database  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:16:53.348Z"),
    "question" : "What is the career scope of Masters in Information Technology in Australia? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 32 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2550c817f0398f9da86"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-will-blockchain-technology-affect-the-information-technology-industry?-",
    "answer" : "Well recently there was an hackthon conducted in our college and we got introduced to the blockchain technology.We submitted a prototype for smart patents implemented using blockchain so in the process of making a prototype we got to know its usage and believe me it is growing rapidly and it is one of the best platform for digital assest. Naveen Chauhan",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:17:25.891Z"),
    "question" : "How will blockchain technology affect the information technology industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 33 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2680c817f0398f9da92"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-information-technology-a-science?-",
    "answer" : "IT is short for Information Technology and is pronounced as separate letters. Information technology is the broad subject concerned with all aspects of managing and processing information, especially within a large organization or company. IT is generally not used in reference to personal or home computing and networking. IT is usually used to describe computers ans computer sciences. It includes all the layers of systems in the organization. Because computer systems are central to information management, computer departments within companies and universities are often called IT departments. Some companies refer to this department as IS (information services) or MIS (management information services). So, yes information technology is a science.   hope this helps, Thank you :) Continue Reading IT is short for Information Technology and is pronounced as separate letters. Information technology is the broad subject concerned with all aspects of managing and processing information, especially within a large organization or company. IT is generally not used in reference to personal or home computing and networking. IT is usually used to describe computers ans computer sciences. It includes all the layers of systems in the organization. Because computer systems are central to information management, computer departments within companies and universities are often called IT departments. Some companies refer to this department as IS (information services) or MIS (management information services). So, yes information technology is a science.   hope this helps, Thank you :) Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:17:44.624Z"),
    "question" : "Is information technology a science? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 34 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f27c0c817f0398f9daa4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-important-problems-in-information-technology-today?-",
    "answer" : "Biggest problem for IT: Teaching people that Information is only a carrier of Knowledge and there is nothing in Information Technology that necessarily conveys Truth. Data is encoded with a Language to create Information that can be conveyed to the User which then needs to Understand the Language to decode Knowledge of the Data. This encoding and decoding of Information is error prone and can result in the User receiving False Knowledge. If multiple Users receive the same Information there is no way to prove that all Users decoded the Information correctly. Misunderstanding even one word can result in False Knowledge. Not everyone has the same definition of \"Information Technology\" but there are a number of questions on Quora that can inform you about important problems in different aspects of IT. For example: What are the seminal papers in distributed systems? Why?What are the best books on network theory?Web 2.0: Where are the most interesting uncharted waters in social software design?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:18:04.668Z"),
    "question" : "What are the important problems in information technology today? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 35 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2a30c817f0398f9dabe"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-information-technology-books?-",
    "answer" : "Start with Why: How Great Leaders Inspire Everyone to Take Action  The inspiring, life-changing bestseller by the author of LEADERS EAT LAST and TOGETHER IS BETTER. In 2009, Simon Sinek started a movement to help people become more inspired at work, and in turn inspire their colleagues and customers. Since then, millions have been touched by the power of his ideas, including more than 28 million who’ve watched his TED Talk based on START WITH WHY -- the third most popular TED video of all time. Sinek starts with a fundamental question: Why are some people and organizations more innovative, more influential, and more profitable than others? Why do some command greater loyalty from customers and employees alike? Even among the successful, why are so few able to repeat their success over an Continue Reading Start with Why: How Great Leaders Inspire Everyone to Take Action  The inspiring, life-changing bestseller by the author of LEADERS EAT LAST and TOGETHER IS BETTER. In 2009, Simon Sinek started a movement to help people become more inspired at work, and in turn inspire their colleagues and customers. Since then, millions have been touched by the power of his ideas, including more than 28 million who’ve watched his TED Talk based on START WITH WHY -- the third most popular TED video of all time. Sinek starts with a fundamental question: Why are some people and organizations more innovative, more influential, and more profitable than others? Why do some command greater loyalty from customers and employees alike? Even among the successful, why are so few able to repeat their success over an Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:18:43.190Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best information technology books? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 36 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2b50c817f0398f9daca"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-is-the-best-site-for-tech-news?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  Which is the best site for tech news?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:19:01.600Z"),
    "question" : "Which is the best site for tech news? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 37 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2c90c817f0398f9dae0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-good-is-the-Master-of-Information-Technology-course-at-Swinburne-University-of-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How good is the Master of Information Technology course at Swinburne University of Technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:19:21.351Z"),
    "question" : "How good is the Master of Information Technology course at Swinburne University of Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 38 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2db0c817f0398f9dae9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-health-information-management-or-health-information-technology-a-lucrative-field?-",
    "answer" : "Yes, it is. Health Information Management Schools are such educational institutes which provide a degree offering a lot of impetus to your existing career in the healthcare industry. This industry and its jobs cannot come to an end because of the changing and even more challenging medical constraints coming up day in day out. Medical expenses are always huge and are also set in various plans and policies which a patient has to take up, because of its unpredictability. What Health Information Management does is, enhances or trains the existing professionals in the healthcare industry to incorporate various strategies in the business of healthcare, and also help render a good career in succession with the degree. Online Health Information Management therefore is a boon to people who are alrea Continue Reading Yes, it is. Health Information Management Schools are such educational institutes which provide a degree offering a lot of impetus to your existing career in the healthcare industry. This industry and its jobs cannot come to an end because of the changing and even more challenging medical constraints coming up day in day out. Medical expenses are always huge and are also set in various plans and policies which a patient has to take up, because of its unpredictability. What Health Information Management does is, enhances or trains the existing professionals in the healthcare industry to incorporate various strategies in the business of healthcare, and also help render a good career in succession with the degree. Online Health Information Management therefore is a boon to people who are alrea Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:19:39.486Z"),
    "question" : "Is health information management or health information technology a lucrative field? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 39 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f2ef0c817f0398f9daf7"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-features-of-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are the features of information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:19:59.321Z"),
    "question" : "What are the features of information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 40 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f3860c817f0398f9db65"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-trending-technologies-in-Information-Technology-at-India-now-a-days?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are trending technologies in Information Technology at India now a days?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:22:30.856Z"),
    "question" : "What are trending technologies in Information Technology at India now a days? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 41 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f3990c817f0398f9db71"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-best-information-technology-businesses?-",
    "answer" : "Here are a few thoughts – I’ll call them the 10 commandments of IT education:  1.\tColleges have a tremendous amount of discretion in what they call their majors and the same major name at two different schools might have completely different courses that are a part of that major. Some IT major fields like Computer Science will include more courses in Programming and advanced Math courses. This all makes it very confusing to answer questions about what a degree is really about unless you can look at all the underlying classes. Computer Information Systems degree (the degree I have) or an Information Technology degree might be very similar or very different – it depends on the school. Another example could be a Computer Network Technology degree might be about configuring network devices li Continue Reading Here are a few thoughts – I’ll call them the 10 commandments of IT education:  1.\tColleges have a tremendous amount of discretion in what they call their majors and the same major name at two different schools might have completely different courses that are a part of that major. Some IT major fields like Computer Science will include more courses in Programming and advanced Math courses. This all makes it very confusing to answer questions about what a degree is really about unless you can look at all the underlying classes. Computer Information Systems degree (the degree I have) or an Information Technology degree might be very similar or very different – it depends on the school. Another example could be a Computer Network Technology degree might be about configuring network devices li Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:22:49.775Z"),
    "question" : "What are the best information technology businesses? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 42 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f3c50c817f0398f9db91"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-latest-technology-in-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Questions Gunjan Yadav",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:23:33.031Z"),
    "question" : "What are the latest technology in Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 43 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f3e90c817f0398f9dbad"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-is-the-master-of-information-technology-program-at-rutgers-business-school?-",
    "answer" : "Kavita Bhat I am currently a student of the same program and If I had to rate it on a scale of 10, I would probably give it a 7. The beauty is its flexibility, I can steer my course to which ever direction I want due to the sheer number of selections. We can take courses from the MBA, CS, IS and PhD departments. The downside is that you don’t have a say on what will be offered in a particular semester, so may be you are all excited on taking Machine Learning but are disappointed because its not being offered. Also, you cant be sure of its availability in the next semester. The other downside is the duration of the program, technically its a 16 month/30 credit course and you need to have 4 each semester to qualify as a full time student. A bad judgement on course selection might lead to grasping for ti Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:24:09.306Z"),
    "question" : "How is the master of information technology program at rutgers business school? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 44 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f3fa0c817f0398f9dbbc"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-responsibilities-of-information-technology-professionals?-",
    "answer" : "Bhavin Modi Primary Responsibilities of IT Security Professionals The job of an IT security professional revolves around protecting IT systems. This includes network, infrastructure, and all other areas of IT. Securing information assets, customer data, financial information, and other critical information is the key responsibility of an IT security professional. In addition to a variety of security tasks, these roles often charge professionals with the responsibility to provide access to information for users based on their necessity and identity. Information is given away to people only when they are legitimately eligible for the access. Every IT security department has certain policies and principles; they follow a set of rules, regulations, methodologies, and strategies to protect information system Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:24:26.302Z"),
    "question" : "What are the responsibilities of information technology professionals? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 45 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f41e0c817f0398f9dbd1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/How-can-the-relationship-between-science-and-technology-be-simply-described?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  How can the relationship between science and technology be simply described?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:25:02.979Z"),
    "question" : "How can the relationship between science and technology be simply described? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 46 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f4300c817f0398f9dbe5"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-next-trend-of-IT?-",
    "answer" : "What are the Future technologies DRONE DELIVERY: We could start seeing delivery drones finally start making deliveries in the next two years.Hyperloop: A Hyperloop could take us in between cities in just six years. We already know we’re getting closer to seeing a Hyperloop, a high-speed propulsion system, after seeing the first test run by start-up Hyperloop One in May. Hyperloop One has actually partnered with the City of Moscow to bring one to Russia.Machine Learning: Machines could start thinking like humans as early as 2025.Space Tours: Space trips designed to send people to Mars could start taking place in 2030.That prediction actually gives Musk some leeway in realizing his vision of getting people to Mars. Musk said at Vox’s Code Conference in June said he plans to send astronauts toContinue Reading What are the Future technologies DRONE DELIVERY: We could start seeing delivery drones finally start making deliveries in the next two years.Hyperloop: A Hyperloop could take us in between cities in just six years. We already know we’re getting closer to seeing a Hyperloop, a high-speed propulsion system, after seeing the first test run by start-up Hyperloop One in May. Hyperloop One has actually partnered with the City of Moscow to bring one to Russia.Machine Learning: Machines could start thinking like humans as early as 2025.Space Tours: Space trips designed to send people to Mars could start taking place in 2030.That prediction actually gives Musk some leeway in realizing his vision of getting people to Mars. Musk said at Vox’s Code Conference in June said he plans to send astronauts toContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:25:20.550Z"),
    "question" : "What is the next trend of IT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 47 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f4440c817f0398f9dbf1"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-computer-engineering-better-than-information-technology-engineering?-",
    "answer" : "I should answer this question. I’m a B.Tech IT student from one of the top institutes in Tamil Nadu and I’m also a Diploma holder in Computer Engineering. So, I have the experience of both. Many outsiders feel that IT is different from Computer Engineering even I felt the same during my UG admissions but the fact is both IT and Computer Engineering are same. Actually most colleges don’t have IT because they don’t have enough students to fill their computer engineering branch so they don’t have IT. The reason behind this is Computer Engineering is created long back(before 4 decades) and seperated from Electronics to make a dedicated course for Computers but IT is introduced in colleges just before 2 decades by making minor changes in Computer Engineering to make it best to support the needs  Continue Reading I should answer this question. I’m a B.Tech IT student from one of the top institutes in Tamil Nadu and I’m also a Diploma holder in Computer Engineering. So, I have the experience of both. Many outsiders feel that IT is different from Computer Engineering even I felt the same during my UG admissions but the fact is both IT and Computer Engineering are same. Actually most colleges don’t have IT because they don’t have enough students to fill their computer engineering branch so they don’t have IT. The reason behind this is Computer Engineering is created long back(before 4 decades) and seperated from Electronics to make a dedicated course for Computers but IT is introduced in colleges just before 2 decades by making minor changes in Computer Engineering to make it best to support the needs  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:25:40.545Z"),
    "question" : "Is computer engineering better than information technology engineering? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 48 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f4550c817f0398f9dbf9"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-type-of-maths-is-needed-to-study-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "You can work in the IT industry and use almost no math at all above what you learned in middle school in the 6th grade. But on the other hand if you are an electrical engineer designing parts that go into say an LCD monitor you need to have done really well in the first to years of university level Calculus and differential equations. Some computer scientist working inputting the limits of AI, find they need to also understand linear aldabra and statistics. But most workers even in some engineering feildsdonrt use much math past the second yea of high school algebra inter day to day work. I think interns f basic thing and very basic Calculus only because I work with robots now. But for years working with security massage systems Used only a general understanding ning or logic and the gener Continue Reading You can work in the IT industry and use almost no math at all above what you learned in middle school in the 6th grade. But on the other hand if you are an electrical engineer designing parts that go into say an LCD monitor you need to have done really well in the first to years of university level Calculus and differential equations. Some computer scientist working inputting the limits of AI, find they need to also understand linear aldabra and statistics. But most workers even in some engineering feildsdonrt use much math past the second yea of high school algebra inter day to day work. I think interns f basic thing and very basic Calculus only because I work with robots now. But for years working with security massage systems Used only a general understanding ning or logic and the gener Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:25:57.410Z"),
    "question" : "What type of maths is needed to study information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 49 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f4680c817f0398f9dc0f"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-does-the-information-technology-branch-involve?-",
    "answer" : "Jean Carlo Garcia  Simply put, IT involves developing continuously simpler ways for businesses and consumers to harness the ever changing technology.. So it involves constant consumer interaction for whoever is doing the role",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:26:16.633Z"),
    "question" : "What does the information technology branch involve? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 50 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f47b0c817f0398f9dc19"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-differences-and-similarities-between-information-science-and-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "According to Florida Tech Online, Information Systems (IS) and Information Technology (IT) are similar fields within Computer Science and are often confused for the same term since IT derived from IS. However, there are some characteristics of each that set them apart.  The Information Systems field typically looks at information or data that comes from a system comprised of computers to help the government or companies reach their goals. In a business setting, IS can include operations support systems or management support systems. However, not all information systems are computer based. Any tools can work together to record information to be considered a system. Careers in IS cover a wide range including analytics, computer security, auditing, programming, and so on.  Information Technolog Continue Reading According to Florida Tech Online, Information Systems (IS) and Information Technology (IT) are similar fields within Computer Science and are often confused for the same term since IT derived from IS. However, there are some characteristics of each that set them apart.  The Information Systems field typically looks at information or data that comes from a system comprised of computers to help the government or companies reach their goals. In a business setting, IS can include operations support systems or management support systems. However, not all information systems are computer based. Any tools can work together to record information to be considered a system. Careers in IS cover a wide range including analytics, computer security, auditing, programming, and so on.  Information Technolog Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:26:35.713Z"),
    "question" : "What are the differences and similarities between information science and information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}
/* 1 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f48f0c817f0398f9dc27"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-next-wave-of-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "Kåre Lohse  Big data is already here but it has legs and will continue to grow in importance. A clear headed multi-faceted approach to encryption and protection of records containing personal information should be getting more attention. General security against hacking has got to be an area where significant contributions can be made. How to position yourself to be at the cutting edge of any of these is another question.",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:26:55.225Z"),
    "question" : "What is the next wave of Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 2 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f4a60c817f0398f9dc41"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-technologies-in-Information-Technology?-",
    "answer" : "If you mean programming languages by technologies, then use this List of programming languages but if you really meant technologies then use this List of technologies !!",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:27:18.064Z"),
    "question" : "What are the technologies in Information Technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 3 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f5100c817f0398f9dc89"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-some-good-advice-for-a-fresher-joining-the-Indian-IT-industry?-",
    "answer" : "Amit Ranjan, Life aint fair yet beautifulAnswered 6 years ago · Author has 86 answers and 205.7K answer viewsWhat is some good advice for a fresher joining the Indian IT industry? Amit Ranjan IT industry is booming in India. Owing to abundance of cheap labor  here, most IT giants have been shifting their base to India post  liberalization. Be it IBM, TCS, Accenture, Cognizant or Capgemini-  all boast of majority of workforce stationed in India. Given the volume  of employment these IT companies generate, chances are fair that you  might land up in an IT firm. IT industry looks too glamorous till you  get to see it inside out. It might seem too lucrative to refuse, but  before you join, you must check if you fit the bill.  Long Working Hours:Post-recession, IT companies expect their employees to work for  atleast 45 hours a week; this would normally exclude your lunch and  off-work hours. Your normal shift timings can be from 8:00am to 6:00pm  or 10:00am to 8:00pm. Essentially aft Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:29:04.866Z"),
    "question" : "What is some good advice for a fresher joining the Indian IT industry? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 4 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f5640c817f0398f9dcc4"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-IT-internet-technology-or-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "The Internet is one of the crucial aspects of our life. It helps in communication between one user to another user from a place to another place. We can share multiple extensible files among us. In general, It abbreviates as NET. Information Technology is a term used to give information about several companies working on plenty of technology. Many of them are shabby and tattered. Thus , companies are starved to increase their markets and shares. It can’t be internet technology because the word IT defines that Information technology. It may not suitable to say Avanish Mane",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:30:28.772Z"),
    "question" : "Is IT internet technology or information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 5 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f5c00c817f0398f9dcfe"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-fundamentals-of-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Allana Alberto Analytical Skills This is a must for every IT professional. Great analytical skills enables us to find ways to solve both complex and small problems. This also can be helpful in developing new plans and ideas.Problem Solving Skills IT professionals are often called to solve problems in networks, software, hardware and they are expected to solve these problems properly since they are the ones who would be able to understand it. You must be able to troubleshoot, find out what causes the problem and the ways to fix it.Memorization Especially for programmers, you must learn and familiarized yourself programming languages and other necessary languages such as mark up languages, query languages or scripting languages.Attention to detail This skill mostly applies to QA. In areas such as web desigContinue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:32:00.817Z"),
    "question" : "What are the fundamentals of information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 6 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f6190c817f0398f9dd44"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-information-technology-law?-",
    "answer" : "To address these questions in reverse order, there is a series of observations collectively referred to as the Law of Information Systems. They refer to the behaviors and patterns of people, technology, software, and any set of procedures within a given system. They are not laws in the legal sense nor are they laws in the scientific or mathematical sense. Technically, it is a social science, as opposed to a physical science such as physics, chemistry, biology, or geology. It covers human behavior, economics, and communication. It is not concerned with biochemistry, earth science, or cosmology. As for the origin of information, this requires a more specific definition of information. To put the problem in perspective, in the broadest sense, a receipt from a grocery store is literature, as is Continue Reading To address these questions in reverse order, there is a series of observations collectively referred to as the Law of Information Systems. They refer to the behaviors and patterns of people, technology, software, and any set of procedures within a given system. They are not laws in the legal sense nor are they laws in the scientific or mathematical sense. Technically, it is a social science, as opposed to a physical science such as physics, chemistry, biology, or geology. It covers human behavior, economics, and communication. It is not concerned with biochemistry, earth science, or cosmology. As for the origin of information, this requires a more specific definition of information. To put the problem in perspective, in the broadest sense, a receipt from a grocery store is literature, as is Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:33:29.250Z"),
    "question" : "What is information technology law? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 7 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f6290c817f0398f9dd4d"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-Java-useful-for-information-technology-students?-",
    "answer" : "Ofcourse, Java is leading language with highest job opportunities. Java uses JVM which takes care of memory allocations and it lacks usage of pointers which makes it a  perfect simple language.Java is widely used in Mobile application development and currently it is widely used in Web services/MVC which include J2EE and frameworks like Spring etc... So it is USEFUL to IT Industry !",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:33:45.588Z"),
    "question" : "Is Java useful for information technology students? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 8 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f6660c817f0398f9dd77"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Is-information-technology-a-boon-or-a-bane?-",
    "answer" : "Anant KumarAnswered 2 years agoIs information technology a boon or a bane? Anant Kumar Why would anyone feel the need to ask if Information Technology is a bane? I'm guessing it has something to do with how the fabric of society is being changed by the rapid development of the IT sector:Privacy issues? Addictive behaviors? A disconnect from reality? Ease of conducting illegal operations?Yes. IT does enable all that. I'm not going to blame human nature for it. We are who we are. Tell us that matter can be converted into a large amount of energy and we are bound to come up with an extinction scale device. However, what IT promises and mostly delivers is well worth the effort that'll need to go into mitigating the damage the aforementioned crisis causes. Any undertaking to be conducted on a large scale requires an elegant means of communication. Anything involving large capital  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:34:46.145Z"),
    "question" : "Is information technology a boon or a bane? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 9 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f69e0c817f0398f9dda0"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-might-you-think-technology-is-a-bad-thing-for-society?-",
    "answer" : "As you are considering about the bad things that came out of technology, let's forget the discovery of monoclonal antibodies that just selectively identifies cancer cells and kill them. Here we consider the bad aspects only.  If we talk about technology, the greatest boom that happened in the last decade was that in mobile technology which directly touched our lives. One day we were composing monophonic ringtones on a Nokia, next day we are navigating to distant lands with our gps. But what changed is, human interaction. The more time we spend with our eyes glued to screen, the less time we spend in our physical lives. We live a dual life, with one feeding on dopamine alone. Yeah, Dopamine is a chemical released in the brain when we are rewarded. That is what gives the high feeling when ouContinue Reading As you are considering about the bad things that came out of technology, let's forget the discovery of monoclonal antibodies that just selectively identifies cancer cells and kill them. Here we consider the bad aspects only.  If we talk about technology, the greatest boom that happened in the last decade was that in mobile technology which directly touched our lives. One day we were composing monophonic ringtones on a Nokia, next day we are navigating to distant lands with our gps. But what changed is, human interaction. The more time we spend with our eyes glued to screen, the less time we spend in our physical lives. We live a dual life, with one feeding on dopamine alone. Yeah, Dopamine is a chemical released in the brain when we are rewarded. That is what gives the high feeling when ouContinue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:35:42.918Z"),
    "question" : "Why might you think technology is a bad thing for society? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 10 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f6af0c817f0398f9ddac"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-technology-has-high-demand?-",
    "answer" : "Here is the list of 8 programs highly in demand in IT sector SAP Those with experience in SAP (an Enterprise Resource Planning or ERP program) will be pleased to know that their skills are not likely to become less desirable any time in the near future. In fact, many industries are in great need of SAP professionals, such as the aerospace, healthcare and defense industries. It has been suggested that demand for SAP professionals is quickly surpassing the supply; and similar to many other programs, there are various areas of specialty within SAP. Those with experience in SAP HANA in-memory databases are perhaps the most in demand, at the moment. Adobe Programs Adobe has released several new programs and software packages that are big right now. Adobe Flex is an open-source program that allows f Continue Reading Here is the list of 8 programs highly in demand in IT sector SAP Those with experience in SAP (an Enterprise Resource Planning or ERP program) will be pleased to know that their skills are not likely to become less desirable any time in the near future. In fact, many industries are in great need of SAP professionals, such as the aerospace, healthcare and defense industries. It has been suggested that demand for SAP professionals is quickly surpassing the supply; and similar to many other programs, there are various areas of specialty within SAP. Those with experience in SAP HANA in-memory databases are perhaps the most in demand, at the moment. Adobe Programs Adobe has released several new programs and software packages that are big right now. Adobe Flex is an open-source program that allows f Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:35:59.228Z"),
    "question" : "Which technology has high demand? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 11 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f6e80c817f0398f9ddd2"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-the-top-paying-IT-jobs?-",
    "answer" : "Tahseen Ahmad Its really good to see that you are motivated to get the highest paid job in the IT industry. The overall IT industry is comprised of various types roles which may offer you a a better career growth. In order to get desired pay package and additional benefits, employees need to train themselves on the correct fields and choose job opportunities that are worth their interest. The salary range is mainly based on the company. There are mainly two kinds of company that pays huge , Very well established companies that spends a bomb to get the best talent in the market.Those startup’s with huge VC investment will spend better than big shots to attract those engineers in the established companies.That being said i know a few software engineers that earn 48 Lakhs + annually( Fixed component)  The expe Continue Reading Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:36:56.986Z"),
    "question" : "What are the top paying IT jobs? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 12 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f6fc0c817f0398f9dde8"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-typical-management-information-systems?-",
    "answer" : "Management Information Systems is actually a profession and not an actual system. Management Information Systems professionals specialize in creating Information Systems in a robust and affordable way. They study and understand how data moves through a larger system. An MIS professional will need to understand the System Development Life Cycle and will study how to increase productivity and quality when creating these systems. They are also the highest paid in the computer professions. The word “Management” is often left off in most contexts. Often the term System Analyst/System Designer can be exchanged with the MIS term and is more popular to see. There is few distinct lines between these professions and often you will find an IT, System Designer, System Analyst, Software Designer and IS  Continue Reading Management Information Systems is actually a profession and not an actual system. Management Information Systems professionals specialize in creating Information Systems in a robust and affordable way. They study and understand how data moves through a larger system. An MIS professional will need to understand the System Development Life Cycle and will study how to increase productivity and quality when creating these systems. They are also the highest paid in the computer professions. The word “Management” is often left off in most contexts. Often the term System Analyst/System Designer can be exchanged with the MIS term and is more popular to see. There is few distinct lines between these professions and often you will find an IT, System Designer, System Analyst, Software Designer and IS  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:37:16.887Z"),
    "question" : "What are typical management information systems? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 13 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f70d0c817f0398f9ddf6"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Which-are-the-best-universities-to-study-information-technology-in-Australia?-",
    "answer" : "The Battle Over List of Colleges in Australia for International Students and How to Win It Given the enormous number of seminars on offer, you are certain to ponder what things to examine in Australia for improved profession prospects. Right now, Australia was recently established for only 14 decades. It is the top migration goal on the planet. Australia is considered as a real part of the best 3 nations where understudies wish to go for extra examinations. It is a standout amongst the best three instruction goals for worldwide understudies. It has probably the best places to think about data innovation courses. Picking Good List of Colleges in Australia for International Students While picking the course understudies consider most surely understood ones without cross-checking the data. Likew Continue Reading The Battle Over List of Colleges in Australia for International Students and How to Win It Given the enormous number of seminars on offer, you are certain to ponder what things to examine in Australia for improved profession prospects. Right now, Australia was recently established for only 14 decades. It is the top migration goal on the planet. Australia is considered as a real part of the best 3 nations where understudies wish to go for extra examinations. It is a standout amongst the best three instruction goals for worldwide understudies. It has probably the best places to think about data innovation courses. Picking Good List of Colleges in Australia for International Students While picking the course understudies consider most surely understood ones without cross-checking the data. Likew Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:37:33.684Z"),
    "question" : "Which are the best universities to study information technology in Australia? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 14 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f71e0c817f0398f9de04"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-is-the-information-technology-scope-at-the-Vellore-campus-VIT?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers Shriansh Srivastava",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:37:50.524Z"),
    "question" : "What is the information technology scope at the Vellore campus VIT? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 15 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f72e0c817f0398f9de10"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/Why-does-information-technology-matter?-",
    "answer" : "Interesting question? My first thoughts go to history and other technological inventions. If we ask? Why did inventing ‘the wheel’ matter? We immediately think of a list of tings from moving stuff to being able to move ourselves in carriages and wagons.Why did inventing ‘the printing press’ matter? We immediately think of communicating ideas and sharing information.Why did ‘discovering how to make and use electricity’ matter? We think of being able to work at night, keep homes and offices warm or cool, and powering devices including washing machines, televisions, can openers, computers, and more.So my reaction is that technology is basic to the being human. It matters because it’s a way for us to explore our potential. Without it we would be more likely to be cold, isolated, hungry, and s Continue Reading Interesting question? My first thoughts go to history and other technological inventions. If we ask? Why did inventing ‘the wheel’ matter? We immediately think of a list of tings from moving stuff to being able to move ourselves in carriages and wagons.Why did inventing ‘the printing press’ matter? We immediately think of communicating ideas and sharing information.Why did ‘discovering how to make and use electricity’ matter? We think of being able to work at night, keep homes and offices warm or cool, and powering devices including washing machines, televisions, can openers, computers, and more.So my reaction is that technology is basic to the being human. It matters because it’s a way for us to explore our potential. Without it we would be more likely to be cold, isolated, hungry, and s Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:38:06.161Z"),
    "question" : "Why does information technology matter? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 16 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f7620c817f0398f9de33"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-some-examples-of-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "Include Related Answers  What are some examples of information technology?",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:38:58.924Z"),
    "question" : "What are some examples of information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}

/* 17 */
{
    "_id" : ObjectId("6034f7740c817f0398f9de46"),
    "job_link" : "https://www.quora.com/What-are-tools-used-in-information-technology?-",
    "answer" : "There are 5 tools used in information technology: Cloud Computing Cloud computing through the provision of internet hosting services has simplified daily tasks much more easily and efficiently. Integrating a cloud into your IT procedures allows you to focus on optimizing the use of your shared resources, saving a lot of time and energy. Mobile technology Mobile technology is a great way to be flexible and have the freedom to run your business anywhere, anytime (with a stable Internet connection). Therefore, investing in mobility tools for your business will not only increase productivity but will also help your team to work more efficiently. Enterprise content management The success of a business depends on its ability to properly store and organize your business information. Enterprise Content  Continue Reading There are 5 tools used in information technology: Cloud Computing Cloud computing through the provision of internet hosting services has simplified daily tasks much more easily and efficiently. Integrating a cloud into your IT procedures allows you to focus on optimizing the use of your shared resources, saving a lot of time and energy. Mobile technology Mobile technology is a great way to be flexible and have the freedom to run your business anywhere, anytime (with a stable Internet connection). Therefore, investing in mobility tools for your business will not only increase productivity but will also help your team to work more efficiently. Enterprise content management The success of a business depends on its ability to properly store and organize your business information. Enterprise Content  Continue Reading",
    "date" : ISODate("2021-02-23T12:39:16.356Z"),
    "question" : "What are tools used in information technology? ",
    "source" : "Quora"
}